Register of the Friedrich A. von Hayek papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Original Accession, 1906-1988
  - Correspondence I, 1923-1988
    - Koestler, Arthur, 1964-1977 (Box-folder 31: 11)
    - Koether, George, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 31: 12)
    - Kogure, Osamu, 1975 (Box-folder 31: 13)
    - Kohler, Ivo, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 31: 14)
    - Koizumi, Shinzo, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 31: 15)
    - Kollek, Teddy, 1982 (Box-folder 31: 16)
    - Kolnai, Aurel T., 1966 (Box-folder 31: 17)
    - Kolnai, Elisabeth, 1976 (Box-folder 31: 18)
    - Komatsu, Kenji, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 31: 19)
    - Konami, Takashi, 1968-1978 (Box-folder 31: 20)
    - Konig, Franz, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 31: 21)
      Includes correspondence with Franz Kreuzer (Österreichischer Rundfunk).
    - Konishi, Tadao, 1963 (Box-folder 31: 22)
    - Kontaktkreis Politik-Wissenschaft-Kultur (Edmund Stoiber, Hübert Wagner), 1977-1981 (Box-folder 31: 23)
    - Konzertdirektion Hans Schlote, 1975-1981 (Box-folder 31: 24)
    - Koopmans, T. C., 1956 (Box-folder 31: 25)
    - Kopp, Karl, 1976-1983 (Box-folder 31: 26)
    - Korea International Economic Institute (J. S. Chung), 1978 (Box-folder 31: 27)
    - Korea Times, 1974-1982 (Box-folder 31: 28)
    - Kornhüber, H. H., 1978-1983 (Box-folder 31: 29)
    - Korninger, S., undated (Box-folder 31: 30)
    - Koryu Ark (Masatoshi Matsushita), 1978 (Box-folder 31: 31)
    - Kratky, Otto, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 31: 32)
    - Kraus, Hans-Christoph, 1983 (Box-folder 31: 33)
    - Krebs, Margaret, 1981 (Box-folder 31: 34)
    - Kreisky, Bruno, 1975 (Box-folder 31: 35)
    - Krelle, W., 1964 (Box-folder 31: 36)
    - Kremer, Johannes, 1987 (Box-folder 31: 37)
    - Kriele, Martin, 1970 (Box-folder 31: 38)
    - Krohn, Klaus-Dieter, 1987 (Box-folder 31: 39)
    - Kroy, Moshe, undated (Box-folder 31: 40)
    - Krusselberg, Hans-Gunter, 1966-1984 (Box-folder 31: 41)
    - Kuehnelt-Leddihn, Erik, 1965-1986 (Box-folder 31: 42)
    - Kung, Emil, 1967 (Box-folder 31: 43)
    - Kunz, Harald, 1976 (Box-folder 31: 44)
    - Kupper, Heinrich, 1978 (Box-folder 31: 45)
    - Kuratorium für die Tagungen der Nobelpreisträger (Lennart and Sonja Bernadotte, Alexander Dees de Sterio), 1974-1987 (Box-folder 32: 1)
      Includes correspondence with Deutscher Akademischer Austauschdienst (Hans Leutner), Informationskreis der Wirtschaft Lindau/Bodensee (Fritz Schlechter), and Ständiger Arbeitsausschuss für die Tagungen der Nobelpreisträger in Lindau (Herr Fleck, Herr Mayr, E. Segatz). Also includes material relating to various meetings of the Tagung der Nobelpreistrager in Lindau (Bodensee), and Hayek's circular of 1981 June 28 entitled "To the participants of the 31st meeting of Nobel Laureates." See also Kastler, Alfred.
    - Lachmann, Ludwig M., 1938-1987 (Box-folder 32: 2)
    - Lakatos, Imre, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 32: 3)
    - Lambsdorff, Otto, 1975 (Box-folder 32: 4)
    - Landert, H., 1978 (Box-folder 32: 5)
    - Lamuraglia, Raul, 1957-1974 (Box-folder 32: 6)
    - Langen, Eugen, 1962 (Box-folder 32: 7)
    - Langenberg, Harry F., 1961-1984 (Box-folder 32: 8)
      Includes correspondence with Mark Wheeler (Washington University Conservative Club).
    - Lank, Alden G., 1980 (Box-folder 32: 9)
    - Laufer, Heinz, 1978 (Box-folder 32: 10)
    - Laufer, Nikolaus K. A., 1984 (Box-folder 32: 11)
    - Lavoie, Donald Charles, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 32: 12)
    - Law and Economics Center (Henry G. Manne, John H. Moore), 1978-1979 (Box-folder 32: 13)
    - Lawson, Nigel, 1978 (Box-folder 32: 14)
    - Leduc, L., 1980 (Box-folder 32: 15)
    - Lee, Ching-lu, 1965 (Box-folder 32: 16)
    - Lee, Orlan, 1963-1975 (Box-folder 33: 1)
    - Leffson, Ulrich, 1966-1985 (Box-folder 33: 2)
    - Leijonhufvud, Axel Stig Bent (and Earlene Craver), 1975-1986 (Box-folder 33: 3)
      Includes correspondence with Antony R. Orme.
    - Lemieux, Pierre, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 33: 4)
    - Lenel, H. O., 1975-1984 (Box-folder 33: 5)
    - Lenk, Hans, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 33: 6)
    - Leonhardt, Fritz, 1975 (Box-folder 33: 7)
    - Leontief, Wassily, 1976 (Box-folder 33: 8)
    - Lepage, Henri, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 33: 9)
    - Letwin, William L. and Shirley R., 1952-1984 (Box-folder 34: 1)
    - Leube, Kurt R., 1975-1985 (Box-folder 34: 2)
      Includes correspondence with Franz Hellbig (Vereinigung Österreichischer Industrieller), Richard Larry (Scaife Family Charitable Trust), and Leonard P. Liggio (Institute for Humane Studies).
    - Leung, Physer, 1981 (Box-folder 34: 3)
    - Leussink, 1966 (Box-folder 34: 4)
    - Levi-Strauss, Claude, 1979 (Box-folder 34: 5)
    - Levin, Bernard, 1980 (Box-folder 34: 6)
    - Levin, Bertram F., 1975 (Box-folder 34: 7)
    - Levitt, Kari, 1982 (Box-folder 34: 8)
    - Levy, David, 1965-1980 (Box-folder 34: 9)
    - Lewis, Russell, 1967 (Box-folder 34: 10)
    - Li, Ming-hsun, 1940-1963 (Box-folder 34: 11)
    - Libby, William L., Jr., 1963 (Box-folder 34: 12)
    - Liberal-Soziale Partei (Franz Marenzi), 1986 (Box-folder 34: 13)
    - Libertarian International, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 34: 14)
    - Libertarian Party (Edward H. Crane, III), 1975-1979 (Box-folder 34: 15)
    - Libertas (Sverre Thon), 1964 (Box-folder 34: 16)
    - Liberty Fund (David Franke, Pierre F. Goodrich, J. Charles King, A. Neil McLeod, Steve Pejovich, Kenneth S. Templeton, Jr.)
      - 1970-1980 (Box-folder 34: 17)
      - 1981-1982 (Box-folder 35: 1)
    - Liebman, Marvin, 1983 (Box-folder 35: 2)
    - Liefmann-Keil, E., 1963-1969 (Box-folder 35: 3)
    - Liga Europa (Franz Riedweg), 1975-1976 (Box-folder 35: 4)
    - Ligeti, Gyorgy, 1984 (Box-folder 35: 5)
    - Lin, Yu-sheng, 1962-1980 (Box-folder 35: 6)
      Includes correspondence with Richard A. Ware (Earhart Foundation).
    - Lingle, Christopher, 1981 (Box-folder 35: 7)
    - Lipsey, Richard G., 1977 (Box-folder 35: 8)
    - Lloyds Bank Review, 1968-1977 (Box-folder 35: 9)
    - Lombard, Jan, 1979 (Box-folder 35: 10)
    - London, Ivan D., 1978 (Box-folder 35: 11)
    - London Interstate Bank (Robert N. Bee), 1982 (Box-folder 35: 12)
    - London School of Economics (Walter Adams, J. Alcock, Anne Bohm, Sydney Caine, Alexander M. Carr-Saunders, Maurice Cranston, Ralf Dahrendorf, P. D. C. Davis, William L. Letwin, Roy K. McCloughry, I. G. Patel, Richard S. Sayers), 1949-1985. 1945 (Box-folder 35: 13)
      Includes correspondence with the British Library of Political and Economic Science, and Hayek's Doctor of Science (Economics) certificate.
    - London Stock Exchange (Nicholas P. Goodison), 1978-1979 (Box-folder 35: 14)
    - Lorenz, Konrad, 1965 (Box-folder 36: 1)
    - Louisiana State University Press (Donald R. Ellegood), 1962 (Box-folder 36: 2)
    - Lucas, J. R., 1973-1984 (Box-folder 36: 3)
    - Luciolli, Mario, 1962 (Box-folder 36: 4)
    - Ludwig-Erhard-Stiftung (Karl Hohmann), 1978-1987 (Box-folder 36: 5)
      Includes Hayek's membership certificate, 1978.
    - Luhnow, Harold W., 1948 (Box-folder 36: 6)
    - Luhrt, Renke, 1982 (Box-folder 36: 7)
    - Lundberg, Erik, 1967-1985 (Box-folder 36: 8)
    - Lunt, James G., 1980-1981 (Box-folder 36: 9)
    - Luppi, Sergio, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 36: 10)
    - Lutz, Vera C., 1938 (Box-folder 36: 11)
    - Lutzeler, Paul Michael, 1982 (Box-folder 36: 12)
    - Lux Mundi [See International Association of University Presidents]
    - Ma, Herbert H. P., 1966 (Box-folder 36: 13)
    - MacCallum, Spencer H., 1977-1983 (Box-folder 36: 14)
    - Macaskill, Fred, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 36: 15)
    - Machan, Tibor R., 1976-1986 (Box-folder 36: 16)
    - Machlup, Fritz
      - 1939-1956 (Box-folder 36: 17)
      - 1962-1983 (Box-folder 36: 18)
    - Mackie, R. A., 1979 (Box-folder 36: 19)
    - Mackworth-Young, G. William, 1979 (Box-folder 36: 20)
    - MacLane, Mr., 1951 (Box-folder 36: 21)
    - Madariaga, Salvador de, 1947-1949 (Box-folder 36: 22)
    - Madecke, Matthias, 1982 (Box-folder 36: 23)
    - Maestri Arredondo, Raul, 1948 (Box-folder 36: 24)
    - Maffitt, Peter C., 1980-1986 (Box-folder 36: 25)
    - Magee, Bryan, 1984 (Box-folder 36: 26)
    - Magg, Herbert, 1963 (Box-folder 36: 27)
    - Mahmoud, Ahmed Fouad, 1965 (Box-folder 36: 28)
    - Mahr, Alexander, 1967 (Box-folder 36: 29)
    - Maier, Hans, 1980 (Box-folder 36: 30)
    - Maier, Karl Friedrich, 1948-1963 (Box-folder 36: 31)
    - Maksoud, Henry and Ilde, 1977-1985 (Box-folder 36: 32)
    - Malagodi, Giovanni, 1985 (Box-folder 36: 33)
    - Malchus, Eva-Maria von, 1971-1984 (Box-folder 36: 34)
    - Mandelbaum, M., 1966 (Box-folder 36: 35)
    - Mann, F. A., 1976-1981 (Box-folder 36: 36)
    - Manne, Henry G., 1986 (Box-folder 36: 37)
    - Marcic, Rene, 1963-1970 (Box-folder 36: 38)
    - Mare F., Alberto di, 1965-1975 (Box-folder 36: 39)
    - Mark Twain Journal, 1969-1979 (Box-folder 37: 1)
    - Markl, Hübert, 1983 (Box-folder 37: 2)
    - Markose, Sheri, 1983 (Box-folder 37: 3)
    - Marks, John, 1980 (Box-folder 37: 4)
    - Marquis, Donald G., 1953 (Box-folder 37: 5)
    - Marshall, Alfred, reprinted article by, 1887; in correspondence from James Blanchard, 1981 (Box-folder 37: 6)
    - Martin, Albert L., 1948 (Box-folder 37: 7)
    - Martin, Dolores T., 1977-1985 (Box-folder 37: 8)
    - Martin, Leonard W., 1978 (Box-folder 37: 9)
    - Martin, Paul C., 1979-1984 (Box-folder 37: 10)
    - Marx, W., 1984 (Box-folder 37: 11)
    - Marzano, Ferruccio, 1984 (Box-folder 37: 12)
    - Masera, Rainer S., re Vera C. Lutz, undated (Box-folder 37: 13)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology Press (Robert Bolick), 1982 (Box-folder 37: 14)
      Includes correspondence with N. Georgescu-Roegen.
    - Mathieu, Vittorio, 1978 (Box-folder 37: 15)
    - Matson, Floyd W., 1960-1964 (Box-folder 37: 16)
    - Matsushita, Konosuke, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 37: 17)
    - Matz, Ulrich, 1976 (Box-folder 37: 18)
    - Maurois, Andre, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 37: 19)
    - Max-Planck-Institut für Experimentelle Medizin (Friedrich Cramer), 1985 (Box-folder 37: 20)
    - May, Hermann, 1977-1985 (Box-folder 37: 21)
    - Maynard, Alan (and Jack Wiseman), 1977 (Box-folder 37: 22)
    - Mayo, Bernard, 1966 (Box-folder 37: 23)
    - Mayr, Ernst, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 37: 24)
    - Mays, W., undated (Box-folder 37: 25)
    - McClellan, Edwin, 1964-1971 (Box-folder 37: 26)
    - McClellan, James, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 37: 27)
    - McCormick, Donald, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 37: 28)
    - McDonald, Lawrence P., 1977-1979 (Box-folder 37: 29)
    - McFalls, John, 1975 (Box-folder 37: 30)
    - McKeon, Professor, 1968 (Box-folder 37: 31)
    - McLendon, Gord, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 37: 32)
    - Meacci, Ferdinando, undated (Box-folder 37: 33)
    - Meade, James, 1977 (Box-folder 37: 34)
    - Medawar, Peter, 1979 (Box-folder 37: 35)
    - Meehl, Paul E., 1956-1963 (Box-folder 37: 36)
    - Meemken, Hermann, 1981 (Box-folder 37: 37)
    - Meet the Press, 1975 (Box-folder 37: 38)
    - Meier, Christian, 1970-1983 (Box-folder 37: 39)
    - Meier, Gerald M., 1983 (Box-folder 37: 40)
    - Meinl, Julius, 1962-1986 (Box-folder 37: 41)
    - Meinl-Collegium (Hans-Paul Nickl), 1963 (Box-folder 37: 42)
    - Melhorn, Wolf-Alexander, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 37: 43)
    - Melitz, Jack, 1963 (Box-folder 37: 44)
    - Mellerowicz, Konrad, 1963 (Box-folder 37: 45)
    - Menano, Horacio, 1984 (Box-folder 37: 46)
    - Menendez, Emilio, 1956-1960 (Box-folder 37: 47)
    - Menger, Chr.-Fr., 1956 (Box-folder 37: 48)
    - Menger, Karl, 1966-1985 (Box-folder 37: 49)
    - Menges, Dietrich Wilhelm von, 1983 (Box-folder 37: 50)
    - Menne, Albert, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 37: 51)
    - Mensa International, 1981 (Box-folder 37: 52)
    - Menuhin, Yehudi, 1985 (Box-folder 37: 53)
    - Mercurio, 1981 (Box-folder 38: 1)
    - Mestmacker, E.-J., 1964-1980 (Box-folder 38: 2)
    - Metall, Rudolf A., 1969 (Box-folder 38: 3)
    - Metzger, Wolfgang, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 38: 4)
    - Meyer, Fritz W., 1951-1956 (Box-folder 38: 5)
      Includes correspondence re Ludwig Erhard.
    - Meyer-Dohm, Peter, 1965 (Box-folder 38: 6)
    - Meyer-Schwickerath, Gerd, 1984 (Box-folder 38: 7)
    - Michener, Roger E., 1976 (Box-folder 38: 8)
    - Middelmann, Hans W., 1978-1983 (Box-folder 38: 9)
    - Mihram, G. Arthur, 1975 (Box-folder 38: 10)
    - Miksch, Leonhard, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 38: 11)
    - Mildt, E. E., 1963 (Box-folder 38: 12)
    - Mill, Anna J., 1949-1950 (Box-folder 38: 13)
    - Miller, E., 1964 (Box-folder 38: 14)
    - Miller, James C., III, 1983 (Box-folder 38: 15)
    - Miller, Loren B., 1947-1953 (Box-folder 38: 16)
    - Miller, Robert, re Lord John Maynard Keynes, 1975 (Box-folder 38: 17)
    - Mills, Ralph J., Jr., 1962-1964 (Box-folder 38: 18)
    - Mills College, 1977 (Box-folder 38: 19)
    - Mineka, Francis E., re John Stuart Mill, 1952-1972 (Box-folder 38: 20)
    - Minogue, Ken, undated (Box-folder 38: 21)
    - Minton, Peter K., 1962 (Box-folder 38: 22)
    - Mintz, Ilse, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 38: 23)
    - Mises, Ludwig von, 1939-1972 (Box-folder 38: 24)
      Includes correspondence with the Royal Economic Society.
    - Mises, Margit von, 1950-1983 (Box-folder 38: 25)
      Includes correspondence with Dr. von Lucius (Gustav Fischer Verlag).
    - Mises Institut (Cynthia M. Dunlevy, Roger W. Garrison, Llewellyn H. Rockwell, Jr.), 1982-1987 (Box-folder 38: 26)
      Includes correspondence with Conrad J. Braun.
    - Mitchell, Janet R., 1975 (Box-folder 38: 27)
    - Mitchell, Wesley C., 1923-1926 (Box-folder 38: 28)
    - Mitterstiller, Dr., 1961 (Box-folder 38: 29)
    - Miyata, Kiyozo, 1964 (Box-folder 38: 30)
    - Moeller, Hero, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 38: 31)
    - Mohler, Armin, 1975 (Box-folder 38: 32)
    - Moldofsky, Naomi, 1985 (Box-folder 38: 33)
    - Molitor, Bruno, 1966-1983 (Box-folder 38: 34)
    - Moller, Johann Michael, 1985 (Box-folder 38: 35)
    - Monday Club (Brian Rathbone), 1978-1980 (Box-folder 38: 36)
    - Monex International (Louis E. Carabini, Patrick M. Boarman), 1975 (Box-folder 38: 37)
    - Monissen, Hans G., 1976 (Box-folder 38: 38)
    - Monk, Ray, 1985 (Box-folder 38: 39)
    - Montes de Oca, Luis, 1948-1954 (Box-folder 38: 40)
      Includes correspondence with Jonathan Cape Ltd., 1945.
    - Moore, Carol, 1983 (Box-folder 38: 41)
    - Moore, Helen G., 1978 (Box-folder 38: 42)
    - Moore, Wilburn L., 1981 (Box-folder 38: 43)
    - Morgan, Charles, 1946-1954 (Box-folder 38: 44)
    - Morgan Bank, 1949 (Box-folder 38: 45)
    - Morgan Guaranty Survey (Milton W. Hudson), 1975-1976 (Box-folder 38: 46)
      Includes correspondence with Wassily Leontieff.
    - Morgenroth, Albrecht, 1983 (Box-folder 38: 47)
    - Morgenstern, Oskar, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 38: 48)
    - Morris, Walter S., 1979-1987 (Box-folder 39: 1)
    - Morrison, Jay, 1958 (Box-folder 39: 2)
    - Morrison, Robert S., 1975-1977 (Box-folder 39: 3)
    - Moschel, Wernhard, 1975 (Box-folder 39: 4)
    - Moser, Simon, 1963-1971 (Box-folder 39: 5)
    - Moss, Laurence S., 1975-1980 (Box-folder 39: 6)
      Includes correspondence with Professor Selden.
    - Mottely, Carlo, 1983 (Box-folder 39: 7)
    - Movimento Nacional de Defesa dos Contribuintes (J. Silva Pereira), 1984 (Box-folder 39: 8)
    - Muccio, Pietro di, 1982 (Box-folder 39: 9)
    - Muhlmann, W. E., 1977 (Box-folder 39: 10)
    - Muller, Horst, 1962 (Box-folder 39: 11)
    - Muller, J. Heinz, 1982 (Box-folder 39: 12)
    - Muller-Armack, Alfred, 1948-1970 (Box-folder 39: 13)
    - Muller-Freienfels, W., 1978 (Box-folder 39: 14)
    - Multi-Currency Society (Robert D. Leakey), 1982 (Box-folder 39: 15)
    - Mun, Kin-chok, 1968 (Box-folder 39: 16)
    - Mundell, Robert A., undated (Box-folder 39: 17)
    - Munkler, Herfried, 1985 (Box-folder 39: 18)
    - Murao, Satoru, 1981 (Box-folder 39: 19)
    - Murata, Toshio, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 39: 20)
    - Murphey, Dwight D., 1978 (Box-folder 39: 21)
    - Murphy Institute of Political Economy (William H. Oakland), 1980 (Box-folder 39: 22)
    - Murray, John, 1955 (Box-folder 39: 23)
    - Musgrave, Gerald L., 1984 (Box-folder 39: 24)
    - Mussey, Barrows, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 39: 25)
    - Nairn, Ronald C., 1979-1981 (Box-folder 39: 26)
    - Nakayama, Sohei, 1966 (Box-folder 39: 27)
    - Nash, George H., 1974 (Box-folder 39: 28)
    - Natanson, Maurice, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 39: 29)
    - National Association of Business Economists (Edgar R. Fiedler, Jerry L. Jordan, Robert T. Parry, James F. Smith), 1980-1984 (Box-folder 39: 30)
    - National Committee for Monetary Reform (James U. Blanchard, III, Nicholas L. Deak), 1975-1983 (Box-folder 39: 31)
    - National Portrait Gallery (John Hayes, Kai Kin Yung), 1981-1983 (Box-folder 39: 32)
      Includes correspondence with Rodrigo Moynihan.
    - National Right to Work Legal Defense Foundation (Herb B. Berkowitz, Edith D. Hakola, Reed E. Larson), 1974-1984 (Box-folder 39: 33)
    - National Tax Limitation Committee, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 39: 34)
    - National Taxpayers Union (James Dale Davidson), 1978 (Box-folder 39: 35)
    - Nationalekonomiska Institutionen vid Lunds Universitet (Bengt Hoglund, Lars Jonung), 1975-1979 (Box-folder 39: 36)
    - Navarro Vazquez, Augustin, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 39: 37)
    - Nederlandsche Bank (Martin M. G. Fase, M. W. Holtrop), 1956-1982 (Box-folder 39: 38)
      Includes correspondence re J. G. Koopmans.
    - Nef, John Ulric, 1948-1968 (Box-folder 39: 39)
      Includes a letter from Evelyn Stefansson Nef, 1979.
    - Neibach, Michael, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 40: 1)
    - Neill, F. P., 1980 (Box-folder 40: 2)
    - Nemo, Philippe, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 40: 3)
    - Network Research (Zeif Smith), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 40: 4)
    - Neue Zurcher Zeitung, 1969 (Box-folder 40: 5)
    - Neumark, F., 1963 (Box-folder 40: 6)
    - Neurath, Otto, 1945 (Box-folder 40: 7)
    - New Japan Securities Co. (Susumu Shoji), undated (Box-folder 40: 8)
    - New Individualist Review [See Raico, Ralph]
    - New York Review of Books (R. B. Silvers), 1973 (Box-folder 40: 9)
    - Newhouse, A. F., 1978 (Box-folder 40: 10)
    - Newman, Theresa, 1964 (Box-folder 40: 11)
    - Niemeyer, Gerhart, 1967 (Box-folder 40: 12)
    - Nippon Hoso Kyokai [See Japan Broadcasting Corporation]
    - Nishimura, Teruo, 1978-1984 (Box-folder 40: 13)
    - Nishiyama, Chiaki, 1957-1985 (Box-folder 40: 14)
    - Nitsche, Rudolf, 1970 (Box-folder 40: 15)
    - Noel-Baker, Philip J., 1955-1960 (Box-folder 40: 16)
    - Noelle-Neumann, Elisabeth, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 40: 17)
    - Nolte, Ernst, 1985 (Box-folder 40: 18)
    - North, Gary, 1968 (Box-folder 40: 19)
    - Nosnik, Abraham, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 40: 20)
    - Nova Spes (Franz Konig), 1986 (Box-folder 40: 21)
    - Nuffield Foundation (John Maddox), 1980 (Box-folder 40: 22)
    - Nymeyer, Frederick, 1962-1970 (Box-folder 40: 23)
    - Oakeshott, Michael, 1949-1968 (Box-folder 40: 24)
    - O'Brien, D. P., 1963 (Box-folder 40: 25)
    - Ockhardt, Kuno, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 40: 26)
    - O'Driscoll, Gerald P., Jr., 1974-1983 (Box-folder 40: 27)
    - Oertzen, Peter von, 1964 (Box-folder 40: 28)
    - Offen, Mrs. Ernest L., 1977 (Box-folder 40: 29)
    - Ogden, F. K., 1962 (Box-folder 40: 30)
    - Ohlin, Bertil, 1974-1977, 1979 (Box-folder 40: 31)
      Includes correspondence with Evy Ohlin.
    - O'Keefe, Byron, 1980 (Box-folder 40: 32)
    - Old Whig Society [See Shenoy, Sudha R.]
    - Olivera, Julio H. G., 1977-1982 (Box-folder 40: 33)
    - Olson, Mancur, Jr., 1966-1979 (Box-folder 40: 34)
    - Olson, Richard, 1970 (Box-folder 40: 35)
    - Onitsuka, Yusuke, 1986 (Box-folder 40: 36)
    - Open Society and Its Friends (William W. Bartley, III, Klaus Pahler, Ivan Slade), 1982-1983 (Box-folder 40: 37)
    - Open University (Alan Gillie), 1980-1983 (Box-folder 40: 38)
    - Orden Pour le Merite für Wissenschaften und Kunste (Kurt Bittel, Helmut Coing, Rudolf Konig, Heinz Maier-Leibnitz), 1977-1987 (Box-folder 41: 1)
      Includes clippings and correspondence with Karl Carstens, Herr Maihofer, and Walter Scheel.
    - Order of Washington (Allen A. Zoll), 1963 (Box-folder 41: 2)
    - Ordo [See Lenel, H. O.]
    - Ornaghi, Lorenzo, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 41: 3)
    - Österreichische Akademie der Wissenschaften (B. Amstadter, Herbert Hunger, Otto Kratky, Karl Lintner, Erwin Ploeckinger, Erich Schmid, Klaus Wundsam), 1970-1980 (Box-folder 41: 4)
    - Österreichische Ludwig Wittgenstein Gesellschaft (Adolf Hubner), 1978-1985 (Box-folder 41: 5)
    - Österreichische Nationalbank (Reinhard Kamitz, Hans Kloss, Herbert Prack, Wolfgang Schmitz), 1959-1977 (Box-folder 42: 1)
      Includes correspondence and clippings re Reinhard Kamitz.
    - Österreichischer Genossenschaftsverband (Wolfgang Gmeiner, Hans Hofinger), 1986 (Box-folder 42: 2)
    - Österreichischer Gewerbeverein (Josef Bittner), 1974-1979 (Box-folder 42: 3)
    - Österreichischer Rundfunk (Franz Kreuzer), 1975-1983 (Box-folder 42: 4)
    - Österreichisches College (Alexander Auer, Otto Molden), 1963-1985 (Box-folder 42: 5)
      Includes correspondence with Fritz P. Molden.
    - Österreichisches Ehrenzeichen für Wissenschaft und Kunst (Otto Kratky), 1976-1987 (Box-folder 42: 6)
    - Österreichisches Institut für Wirtschaftsforschung (Felix Butschek, Franz Nemschak, Hans Seidel), 1967-1980 (Box-folder 42: 7)
    - O'Sullivan, John, undated (Box-folder 42: 8)
    - Otto-Suhr-Institut (Walter Krumholz), 1963 (Box-folder 42: 9)
    - Owens, E. S., 1977 (Box-folder 42: 10)
    - Oxford Union Society, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 42: 11)
    - Pacheco, Claudia Bernhardt de Souza, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 42: 12)
    - Pacific Institute (Charles W. Baird, Maurice Mann, David J. Theroux) [See also O'Driscoll, Gerald P., Jr.], 1978-1987 (Box-folder 42: 13)
    - Packe, Michael St. John, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 42: 14)
    - Padoa, Fabio, 1984 (Box-folder 42: 15)
    - Padoa-Schioppa, Tommaso, 1985 (Box-folder 42: 16)
    - Pahler, Klaus, 1985 (Box-folder 42: 17)
    - Paish, Frank, 1969 (Box-folder 42: 18)
    - Pais, 1983 (Box-folder 42: 19)
    - Palmer, Robert R., 1968 (Box-folder 42: 20)
    - Paneuropa-Union (Roland Coudenhove-Kalergi), 1966 (Box-folder 42: 21)
    - Patinkin, Don, 1984 (Box-folder 42: 22)
    - Pattee, H. H., 1983 (Box-folder 42: 23)
    - Patterson, Lawrence T., 1978-1983 (Box-folder 42: 24)
    - Paul, Ron, 1975-1985 (Box-folder 43: 1)
    - Paulson, Dennis, 1983 (Box-folder 43: 2)
    - Pauly, Mark V., 1966 (Box-folder 43: 3)
    - Pazos, Luis, 1980 (Box-folder 43: 4)
    - Peacock, Alan, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 43: 5)
    - Pejovich, Svetozar, 1978-1986 (Box-folder 43: 6)
    - Pelikan, Pavel, 1980 (Box-folder 43: 7)
    - Pelzmann, Linde, 1985 (Box-folder 43: 8)
    - Pendse, Shripad, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 43: 9)
    - Perroux, Francois, 1956-1980 (Box-folder 43: 10)
    - Perschke, Walter, 1977 (Box-folder 43: 11)
    - Peters, Lovett C., 1962 (Box-folder 43: 12)
    - Peters, Richard S., 1962 (Box-folder 43: 13)
    - Peterson, William H., 1982 (Box-folder 43: 14)
    - Petro, Sylvester, 1965-1982 (Box-folder 43: 15)
    - Peutinger Collegium (Gerhard Constantin Treutlein), 1984-1985 (Box-folder 43: 16)
      Includes correspondence with Ulrich van Lith.
    - PHayeklberg, Bernhard, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 43: 17)
    - Pfannschmidt, Martin, 1983 (Box-folder 43: 18)
    - Pfaundler, Wolfgang, 1963-1984 (Box-folder 43: 19)
    - Pfister, Bernhard, 1963-1975 (Box-folder 43: 20)
    - Pfleiderer, Otto, 1968 (Box-folder 43: 21)
    - Philadelphia Society (John A. Howard, Russell Kirk, Don Lipsett), 1965-1985 (Box-folder 43: 22)
      Includes correspondence with Pierre F. Goodrich (Liberty Fund).
    - Philip, Winifred M., 1976-1986 (Box-folder 43: 23)
    - Phillips, H. B., 1956 (Box-folder 43: 24)
    - Phillips, Hugh S., 1977 (Box-folder 43: 25)
    - Pick, Franz, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 43: 26)
    - Pietrucha, Jerzy, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 43: 27)
    - Pinschof, Karl, 1975 (Box-folder 43: 28)
    - Pixis, Karlheinz, 1983 (Box-folder 43: 29)